[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Coyote is also known as The Prairie Wolf.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1981 people with AIDS were diagnosed with the term GRID. What did GRID mean?", "correct_answer": "Gay-Related Immune Deficiency", "incorrect_answers": ["Great Risk of Immune Disease", "Grave Risk of Immune Deficiency", "Grievous Ravishing Immune Disease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Four can be half of five.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hypergiants, the largest stars known to scientists, have a mass up to how many times that of the Sun?", "correct_answer": "100", "incorrect_answers": ["30", "10", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Star Wars movies is Obi-Wan alive in?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "6", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a group of bears called?", "correct_answer": "a sleuth", "incorrect_answers": ["a family", "a tribe", "a band"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of Galaxy is the Milky Way?", "correct_answer": "Barred Spiral", "incorrect_answers": ["Elliptical", "Spiral", "Irregular"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Common sage, also known as Garden sage, was found to be beneficial in mild to moderate cases of this dangerous disease.", "correct_answer": "Alzheimers disease", "incorrect_answers": ["Malaria", "Hepatitis", "AIDS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does ochlophobia mean fear of diseases?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What place of business was turned into a prison camp for residents of Calumet in the film Red Dawn?", "correct_answer": "Drive In Theater", "incorrect_answers": ["Municipal Parking Lot", "City Park", "Football Stadium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The temperature on the Moon reaches 243\u00b0 F at midday on the lunar equator.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Measuring at the Equator, what is the closest approximation of the Earths circumference?", "correct_answer": "24,900 miles", "incorrect_answers": ["24,900,000 miles", "249,000 miles", "2,490,000 miles"]}]